{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": "b5c19d3c-69ac-46db-8020-f06c7772b30f",
      "title": "Transmitting",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?69069",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to compress?",
          "answer": "Use the bluetooth JSON transmitter, then you can copy the bluetooth circuit!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to generate?",
          "answer": "The XSS program is down, parse the 1080p transmitter so we can bypass the USB circuit!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to bypass?",
          "answer": "Use the redundant GB hard drive, then you can hack the virtual alarm!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-02-21T10:09:56.053Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "15bfbab2-aab0-469b-b67c-08a01a4f09ee",
      "title": "Navigating",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?5146",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to calculate?",
          "answer": "overriding the program won't do anything, we need to connect the optical IB feed!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to copy?",
          "answer": "compressing the matrix won't do anything, we need to connect the auxiliary JBOD card!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to override?",
          "answer": "transmitting the feed won't do anything, we need to override the mobile JSON monitor!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-03-02T08:51:17.687Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "f44d3ef7-8f52-4388-a500-85ecfb4b100e",
      "title": "Bypassing",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?770",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to input?",
          "answer": "quantifying the system won't do anything, we need to bypass the solid state SDD transmitter!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to synthesize?",
          "answer": "You can't quantify the program without generating the mobile FTP card!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to index?",
          "answer": "Try to parse the GB monitor, maybe it will program the optical program!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-02-24T17:54:30.978Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "6cc09165-ba40-4888-acf8-c2ffaff0c511",
      "title": "Compressing",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?20287",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to input?",
          "answer": "Try to connect the RAM transmitter, maybe it will bypass the online system!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to synthesize?",
          "answer": "If we program the array, we can get to the AGP port through the wireless ADP firewall!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to parse?",
          "answer": "The XSS card is down, generate the virtual feed so we can override the USB hard drive!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-01-05T09:48:37.796Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9b40c07-fc00-448b-98c3-71893b31a38b",
      "title": "Connecting",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?61069",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to hack?",
          "answer": "If we back up the capacitor, we can get to the SMS transmitter through the mobile FTP driver!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to bypass?",
          "answer": "I'll override the cross-platform AGP microchip, that should panel the IB firewall!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to generate?",
          "answer": "Try to copy the EXE port, maybe it will back up the digital matrix!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-02-06T11:26:41.780Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "85e45956-b53b-41f6-af93-f33b8196451f",
      "title": "Calculating",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?53063",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to back up?",
          "answer": "You can't program the microchip without navigating the redundant PCI circuit!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to copy?",
          "answer": "Try to input the FTP matrix, maybe it will calculate the haptic protocol!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to synthesize?",
          "answer": "backing up the bandwidth won't do anything, we need to calculate the online THX hard drive!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-02-07T18:43:14.014Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "57910fef-1031-441b-b546-1a1b4a7728cb",
      "title": "Backing up",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?88724",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to calculate?",
          "answer": "navigating the program won't do anything, we need to override the virtual AI driver!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to reboot?",
          "answer": "We need to bypass the virtual SMS capacitor!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to quantify?",
          "answer": "Use the primary XML feed, then you can compress the back-end capacitor!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-02-04T13:45:42.782Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "247bcd62-9864-411e-a740-0215a70da7a4",
      "title": "Synthesizing",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?55073",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to connect?",
          "answer": "Try to navigate the AI hard drive, maybe it will program the neural protocol!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to index?",
          "answer": "Try to back up the PNG pixel, maybe it will navigate the wireless alarm!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to generate?",
          "answer": "Use the optical XSS hard drive, then you can copy the cross-platform matrix!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-03-02T11:28:09.008Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "8d542483-4ccd-4f2c-ae7f-0a357ba5ea16",
      "title": "Overriding",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?6922",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to reboot?",
          "answer": "The EXE sensor is down, program the auxiliary bus so we can copy the ADP transmitter!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to back up?",
          "answer": "I'll calculate the online COM card, that should application the IB bandwidth!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to override?",
          "answer": "I'll hack the haptic SCSI pixel, that should card the FTP microchip!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-01-26T15:59:19.983Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "05aebd80-604d-4206-a6ea-cf12486e9d6e",
      "title": "Backing up",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?26722",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to hack?",
          "answer": "Use the virtual XML firewall, then you can hack the primary port!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to index?",
          "answer": "We need to override the bluetooth SAS firewall!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to index?",
          "answer": "The SCSI pixel is down, override the optical card so we can override the GB alarm!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-02-23T01:51:29.019Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "367e3bb8-65f4-45c2-b200-8e956fab70e1",
      "title": "Compressing",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?75380",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How to calculate?",
          "answer": "If we calculate the port, we can get to the XML monitor through the bluetooth THX pixel!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to quantify?",
          "answer": "You can't quantify the system without calculating the neural SQL pixel!"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to synthesize?",
          "answer": "You can't parse the matrix without synthesizing the wireless SSL array!"
        }
      ],
      "timestamp": "2019-02-18T12:54:09.453Z"
    },
    {
      "id": "c85bca43-a872-41ed-a3ca-5f46d46d1611",
      "title": "teedy",
      "imgUrl": "http://lorempixel.com/720/1440/technics?86777",
      "cards": [],
      "timestamp": 1551563156825
    }
  ]
}